trendmx.com 2010-06-21

# Trendmetrix Software Privacy Policy

|  | SEO Company  
---  
   
| 

## TrendMetrix Software Inc. Privacy Policy

TrendMetrix is committed to user privacy in its products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy.

This policy covers TrendMetrix's corporate web site. TrendMetrix encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit. Below is a summary of TrendMetrix's online privacy policy. 

## Types and uses of personal information

  * Customer Feedback and Support. 
    * Provides a mechanism for requesting information from TrendMetrix. Also used to tell us how we can improve our products, services and site designs.
  * Email Correspondence. 
    * Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information about TrendMetrix, our products, and services.
  * Event Registration. 
    * Provides a mechanism for requesting information from you to register in special events.  
We will only use your personal information in the ways specified when it was collected. We will not subsequently change the way in which we use your personal information, unless you consent to the new usage.

## Security Measures

We protect the personal information you share with us. For example, if you make an online purchase with us, we encrypt your credit card number. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. 

Authorized third party agents may also need access to some of your personal information.   
For example, if we need to dispatch something to you, we must share your name and address with a courier company. We provide third parties with only the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.

## Data Retention

TrendMetrix will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

## Linked Web Sites

We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

## Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

## Cookies

The TrendMetrix Web site uses cookies. Cookies help us to provide you with targeted information by measuring which Web site areas are of greatest interest. TrendMetrix also uses cookies when you register for certain Web promotions. In this situation, a cookie will store useful information that enables our Web site to remember you when you return. TrendMetrix can only read cookies from TrendMetrix Web sites. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of our Web sites. Some Web sites will not allow you to complete certain activities if cookies are disabled. For example, our consumer e-commerce site uses session cookies and persistent cookies to process transactions. If you do not accept cookies, the associated shopping bag will not work and you would not be able to order.   

|
